Hey everyone, welcome to Ethical Hacking of Consumer and differential Security.
I am Ajay and I will be getting you through this complete cyber security journey.
So in this course, you will not only learn how hackers attack, but also how different
users protect mastering both sides of security. We will start with the data communication
and I mean the networking, then we will move on to the retaining concepts based on
might or like exploitation, related escalation, even malware development. Also, in the
similar sections, so once you perform the attack in the target machine, so parallely you
will be investigating what you have done in the retaining. So how you attack? What are
the things you have used? What are the commands you have executed? So everything in the
end of the section, you will be investigating like a new team. Basically, in this course
you are going to learn how to attack, how to defend, how to respond, and how areas and
antivirus software will work, how the analyst will perform the investigation in the end.
So this course is for everyone, anyone who wants to hand on practical cyber security knowledge,
even students, IT professionals and aspiring ethical hackers, so retainers, the detection
engineers and everyone. So by this end of this course, you are very confident in setting
up your lab, executing controlled attacks, and responding like professional defenders,
even developing malicious program that will evade antivirus software and EDR platforms.
So, let's get started, and let's build your complete cyber security skill set together.
Thanks for watching this video, and thanks for enrolling the course. And one more thing,
my advice, don't provide a feedback now, watch all the videos, complete the course,
and at the end of the course, please give me feedback for the course. So never ever provide
a feedback by watching two or three videos, complete the course, and the end of the course,
please provide the feedback. So thanks for watching, and we will see you guys in the next video.
Thank you, bye bye.